

NGUYEN THANH TUNG

Fresher Java Web



Apply the acquired knowledge to the development of quality software. At the same time, accumulate experience and knowledge to meet the needs of higher positions. Ready to learn new programming language to serve the needs of work and upgrade my skills

Contact information

Oct 25, 1999

thanhtungnguyen913@gmail.com

0398851652

http://bit.ly/3XfJtsd

144 Ton That Son, Huong Thuy, TT Hue

Skills

- Advanced skills
- Java Core
- -00P
- Spring Boot
- RESTful API
- Servlet and JSP, JSTL
- JDBC
- MySQL
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JQuery, AJAX Basic
- Spring Framework Basic
- Spring Data JPA Basic
- JavaScript, ReactJS Basic, NodeJS Front End

Soft skills

- Ability to work independently and in a team
- Quickly adapt to the working environment, get along quickly.
- Withstand high work pressure.
- Organize, plan and manage time.
- Problem-solving skills.
- Self-study and search skills.

Education

• UNIVERSITY OF ECONOMICS - HUE UNIVERSITY

Financial accountant 09/2017-09/2020

Graduated - GPA 2.34

• CODEGYM HUE PROGRAMMING TRAINING CENTER

Developer 02/2022-11/2022

- Join the course "Bootcamp Java WEB", after more than 1000 hours of learning and practicing, I have learned and matured, developed soft skills and technical skills.
- Trained in effective teamwork skills and gained experience through small projects that included management tools such as Kanban and the application of Scrum principles to projects.

Work experience

• TEXTILE GARMENT INVESTMENT JOINT STOCK COMPANY - THIEN AN PHAT

Intern - General Accounting 03/2019-07/2019

- Perform other duties as assigned by the company's chiefaccountant.
- Participate in and coordinate the periodic internalinspection and control.
- Prepare monthly tax declaration dossiers, quarterly financialstatements, annual tax finalization dossiers, and annual financialstatements as prescribed.
- Provide data to leaders and functional units when required.

CODEGYM

Student 10/2022-11/2022

Office information

- Proficient in using Word, Excel, Power Point,...

Language

- English level B1 (Listening, speaking, reading and writing is good)
- Certificate of completion of courses at Codegym:

http://bit.ly/3RGZOFy

Interests

- · Watch movie
- · Eating.
- · Play game.
- Play football.
- Travel and explore.

Reference person

• Mr. NGUYEN HUU ANH KHOA

- Director of CodeGym Hue Center
- Phone: 0935 216 417
- Email: Khoa.nguyen@codegym.vn

Project: MEGA FARM - CLEAN FOOD STORE

• **Deployment time**: 1 month

• Number of members: 3 members

• Applied knowledge:

- MySQL - Database

- Spring Boot - API

- NodeJs - Dashboard

- React - Client

- jQuery

- Bootstrap 4

• Position: Member

- Analyze and design application architecture with the team.
- Manage tasks and group discussions via Jira, Slack.
- Application development according to Scrum model standards.
- Teams using Git Source Version Management.
- Report daily work to Coach.
- Build function to create, delete, edit for: Employee.
- Display customer list Build order management function, change order status, create POS for offline sales.
- Revenue statistics and related items
- Cut the interface for DashBoard page.
- Brief description:

This is a clean food store management system with the following features:

- The dashboard is for administrative users, admin can use all the functions of the system and the employee is the person with limited features, only using some functions (if there is access to the link below). for admin an error page will be displayed)
- Dashboard page provides many subpages with more than 60 functions for users to easily manage products as well as inventory statistics and business status.
- A client page for customers to use. Customers can view and order products on sale. In addition, to help customers choose the desired product, the customer page has the function of filtering by price, brand, and other specifications.
- Link set function description: http://bit.ly/3YrKdf1
- watch video description about project if link crashed: (<u>https://bit.ly/3HWHMdM)</u>

• Link product:

-Client: <u>http://bit.ly/40CWS0H</u> Email: customer@gmail.com

Password: 123123

- Dashboard: https://bit.ly/3REP4Hp

+ Account Admin: Email: bob@co.cc Password: 123 +Account User: Email: camap@co.cc Password: 12345678

(Note: Customers can view products, add products to the cart and can view and change the cart, but customers who want to pay for products in the cart must log in to their account (or register if you do not have an account) will be paid for the product.)

. I inkait:

- Link Dashboard: http://bit.ly/3lhFA9f
- Link Client: http://bit.ly/3wZUWS2

CODEGYM

Student 07/2022-7/2022

- Project: TT-STORE TECHNOLOGY MANAGERMENT (v1)
- Deployment time: 1 week
- Link Github: http://bit.ly/3YrqhsE
- Main function:- Login to Admin account add, edit, delete, search products, paginate, sort products
- Applied knowledge: Java, Jsp, Servlet, MySql, BootStrap

CODEGYM

Student 08/2022-8/2022

- Project: TT-STORE TECHNOLOGY MANAGERMENT (v2)
- **Deployment time**: 1 week
- Link Github: https://bit.ly/3PSarn0
- General introduction:
- With the same features as version 1, but using and accessing new technologies. From there can more or less draw experience, to develop for future projects.
- Applied knowledge: Spring Boot, Spring Security, Spring Data JPA, jQuery-AJAX, Bootstrap 4, mô hình MVC.

CODEGYM

Student 06/2022-06/2022

- Project: LAO FOOD MANAGER
- Deployment time: 1 week
- Link Github: http://bit.ly/3YlpyJA
- Main function:
- Register, login user account
- Add, edit, delete, search, sort list of users, products
- Block, unlock user accounts
- Applied knowledge: Java Core, OOP

CODEGYM

Student 04/2022-04/2022

- Project: SALES WEBSITE CARLSBERG BEER
- **Deployment time**: 1 week
- Link Github: https://bit.ly/3PTDJ5n
- Main function:
- Show website homepage
- Display product list, search products, add products to cart
- Applied knowledge: html, css, JavaScript